no jumper coolest podcast in the world
and today we got a a legendary man in
the building jpeg mafia thank you man
appreciate it how are you doing
i'm good
been arguing with
women all morning really
so i'm in a weird head space but yeah
i'm good that's interesting that's good
to know you're out here just like having
human experiences like that because
listen to your music sometimes it's like
it's hard for me to imagine what your
life is actually like
um
right now my life is pretty boring but
it used to be pretty hectic but uh i
mostly just
talk about you from that perspective but
yeah right now i mean i'm 30 i'm i'm old
so like i just do 30 year old [__] right
so your your wild days are behind you
you really feel that way
kinda
a little bit like when i was if i
i was talking to somebody about this the
other day but if i had
the [__] that kids have now like
tick-tock and etc like when i was like
in high school right
i could it could have been a whole
different thing for me right but like
yeah now
i don't really do much now like infinite
creative outlets for them and when i
think about my childhood i was really
like looking for anything like that you
know i wanted to have a voice i wanted
to make content i wanted to you know
without really understanding that
because it was just so much harder to do
that yeah but back when like um the
internet was more barren back in the day
it was like you remember like rotten.com
and [__] like that like it was like that
was the most interesting thing online at
the time when i was a kid you know what
i mean now it's like
you could that [__] is nothing no people
wouldn't bat an eye and no [__] like
that but yeah if if i was in high school
with like all the [__] you could do now
making a youtube page yeah i could have
probably been famous for something else
and i see that like i'll see a meme page
for the most [__] random thing of you
know a fan page of some artist and it'll
have like 50 000 followers just from
making memes consistency
there's a dude who sends me late he
sends celebrities legos on instagram
every day he's like i'm going to send
this select every celebrity a lego for
100 days and he has certain amount of
followers just because he's consistent
wow it doesn't even mean [__] right
but yeah but is being an influencer and
being an artist these days like too
close you seem like you probably aren't
super comfortable with the fact that you
the stomach center kind of a billboard
for yourself your your content as well
as potentially other brands
um
i mean
they were gonna it was gonna do that
anyway you know what i mean like
my opinion of it doesn't really matter
is like artists and influencers were
always going to like mix because there's
always [__] that's always like oh i do
this this and this so eventually
you know
with all the tools we have now
eventually
people are going to start doing that for
real like i actually do all this [__] so
i i don't know it's it was just bound to
happen because you're one of the few
artists that and learning about you that
have seen that you actually had this
contentious relationship with fame where
like you felt kind of uncomfortable with
it once everybody just started to
gravitate towards your [__] where i feel
like very few artists that i've spoken
to have like the self-awareness to
really get that
yeah i'm just too normal to be honest
like
in my
like when i started getting any money
from music i was like 28 29 right so by
that time i'm a grown-ass man
i have
already lived enough life to not be
[__] over or like tricked into [__] so
like [__] just annoys me most of the
time like in the industry but um yeah
i'm constantly thinking that i want to
see young artists blow up and they just
sort of their personality gets frozen in
time at like 18 yeah and they never like
understand what it is to be an adult or
to have to work a shitty job or whatever
and that just colors the whole rest of
their life yeah me i had worked infinite
shitty jobs i actually did it the hard
way i guess that's why i'm just kind of
like whatever you know right so like you
know i was performing for years had so
many jobs i was literally trying to make
money from this for so [__] long
right by the time i actually started
making money from it i was just like
got it but your music to me doesn't
really sound like somebody trying to
make money off their music
no that that wasn't the end seems like
you would have made a lot of different
choices aesthetically et cetera if you
are really just trying to get paid a lot
of the rappers i interview seem like
they're just trying to make some money
yeah yeah no i'm i'm not just trying to
get paid i actually just like what i do
the getting paid [__] is a byproduct of
it i do want money so i can live but
like i'm not out here like
i just need the money i'm only in it for
the money type [__] right but i'm always
having that conversation with people
about how the older you get
the less like when you're young when
you're 18 19 it seems like everything's
about
really like popularity and just meeting
people and girls and being around [__]
etc and then as you get closer to your
30s well into your 30s it starts to
things start to seem a bit more simple i
know so many people have basically like
built up a life for themselves a
platform and then at some point in their
early 30s they just pivot out of it
because they realize they're not ever
going to make a significant amount of
money doing that
yeah it's
that's another byproduct of just doing
[__] like on camera all the time you get
frozen like whatever people think of you
their first impression is just that's it
yeah and if you're yeah if their first
impression of you is some [__] you were
doing you were 17
that's probably difficult some child
star [__] yeah
you got a lot of eyeballs on you that
are very uh
discerning as well like i was watching a
video of some [__] white kid with
glasses just talking about your career i
hate those videos dude and i was like
hey it kind of says a lot about your
content that people are even making
these kind of videos most rappers i
interviewed just don't have this type of
analysis going into their their art
but it also just seemed like so much
pressure because they're just talking
about like i feel like with this project
he he is fully formed like this is it i
don't know how he's going to improve
upon this i'm like wow that's a lot of
[__] pressure it's it's it's really
not it's people people
i think
the type of music i make it's just kind
of weirder and more like
left field so it's just naturally going
to attract that kind of person you know
i feel like you attract like aspiring
music journalists who want who want to
be verbose and discussing
what they are taking in you know yeah
it's so unfortunate but yeah i i really
do feel like i attract people who want
to work not all that's all i track but
there's a large a minority of people
that are just like yeah just like that
and um yeah just that's a byproduct of
just making weird [__] it's the same
thing like um what's it like technine
the rapper technology right like he puts
on masks and like wears [__] like that
and it's just like yeah you're gonna
attract
the white kids with glasses when you do
[__] like that's true so i understand
and then as far as them the pressure
it's not really any pressure people hear
what i want them to hear so if they're
judging [__] based on like what i've let
them hear already it's like you haven't
heard what i'm doing in private so it's
like i don't really care you know what i
mean like you're just hearing like what
i
you're judging me based on specifically
what i wanted you to right so like you
don't know anything else so if you have
100 songs
the ones that make it onto the project
are those going to be the ones that are
more left field or do the weirdest songs
tend to not make the project no the
weirdest [__] gets uh stuffed in because
i already have a reputation as being
like
too weird for some people right so
i just tuck most of that in because it's
maybe insecurity but like no i i
actually try to put out [__] that sounds
more normal to my ears and then when
when it comes out people are just like
what is this [__]
is that that happens every single time i
put out something i'm just like yeah
this sounds like
this i don't know this sounds like a
baby song or something [__] like to to
me and then i put it out and they're
just like this is the strangest thing
i've ever heard man tuck it back in are
you just chronically bored with like
mainstream popular rap for the most
absolutely yeah
i keep getting closer and closer to
being able to admit that so yeah
yeah
and i don't mean it in like a
old headway it's just actually it's not
interesting to me from a technical
perspective right for the most part it's
just like
i don't care a lot of what sells right
now you probably know because you cover
a lot of these dudes but a lot of what
sells now is personality yeah it's a lot
of people like what's going on outside
of this [__]
you know what your real life is they
want authenticity to like match with the
rhymes but the actual music itself is
not evolving at all so like yeah it
doesn't interest me yeah it it it
interests me on that level like oh this
dude's really real but like there's
another part of me that's just like this
shit's boring on like a technical level
yeah i mean like hip-hop has kind of
replaced uh you know technical
competency or artistry with like
successfulness and and character for the
most part those are like the easier
things for
the fans to sort of wrap their head
around i guess and and i also feel like
it's the kind of thing where the same
way that they were able to teach a
computer to play chess better than any
human being it's like the algorithm will
lead you to the conclusions of what
music is actually going to
you know do well and that's why even
even artists who seem like they're a
little bit artistic or have different uh
aesthetic choices that they plan on
making they'll be out in the game for a
couple years and you just sort of watch
their production just gravitate back
towards the sort of core of rap because
that's the thing that's most attractive
to people you know yeah it usually just
kind of bounces back to that you're
right even even with me like i probably
made weirder [__] back in the day and um
if you listen to my stuff now it
probably sounds
to someone who's been listening to me
for years this [__] now probably sounds
like
a pop album to them you know to someone
who listens to weird [__] all the time
but yeah watching that happen to thug
throughout my life has been kind of
watching the thing watching thugs career
oh thug's career i mean he was the most
abrasive rapper ever and i loved him for
that early on
he it's interesting because his career
has gone from like
people being like what the [__] is this
to now it's just this um
baseline respect that people have for
him like it's just like yeah you don't
thug you know what i mean yeah
i guess like seeing that from where it
was to now it's just people are such
dick right as you know because yeah the
um
the reception to him was completely
different before but he always had
people supporting him because he's
always like he's extremely talented he's
never changed but yeah i mean he was the
kind of guy where honestly even if his
music sucked i feel like he still would
have been famous because he was just
that endearing of a character he yeah
he's he's pretty just kind of
interesting outside of
just music itself right his music is
actually crazy though like the way he
he's an underrated rapper the way he
raps is like really really weird yeah
probably like the most influential
rapper like the last 10 years i would
say
really you think so him and who little b
yeah but don't you feel like the the the
shadow of little b has been kind of
limited which i feel like is a shame but
he makes no effort to be in the public
eye he doesn't do any of the stuff that
you would expect somebody in his
position to do which is very that's him
that's what makes him him he's never
made the choices you would have expected
from him but sometimes i feel like
the younger audience has kind of lost
sight of how important he was yeah he um
he he kind of has this aura of i already
did it like i don't have to do it like
my influence is there i don't have to do
much right and i'm just i think people
just respect it but yeah yeah maybe
young thug who else
yeah i can't think of it right now but
yeah that could probably be the most
yeah i mean we could sit here all day
probably think of some other good ones
chief keith definitely for sure yeah
um but okay like
you seem like a smart enough dude that
like a lot of rappers claim that they
don't read the
meta commentary about themselves oh i do
i don't believe that you would be able
to ignore it you just seem like the kind
of guy who gets fascinated by it yeah
they are they're all lying you know
everyone i mean i've
been around people who are extremely
famous and they read that [__] so i'm
just like i know you [__] that are
under that are reading that [__] but
yeah i absolutely read it especially if
it's on my
if you at me
you know i'm definitely going to look at
it but it's it gives you a general
perception of
what people think of you i mean yeah it
gives a general perception of like the
idea of you out there right because you
can think you're a certain way like in
my head i'm a certain way but to people
on the internet and on the outside i'm
like probably just a weirdo right but do
you put a lot of thought into how you
present yourself on social media because
i feel like that that's that's a huge
part of what your brand is and if you
were acting silly on your instagram
story every day then that basically
would change the way that you're viewed
you know no i get drunk and i do various
drugs and i just log into my twitter
account
and just do whatever i actually hold
back a lot on my twitter i could like
i could easily get myself kicked out of
the industry like
like that but like yeah easily but um
no i just you know do drugs and get
online and say whatever really that's a
mess right there
like getting drunk and being on twitter
and just saying the craziest [__] that
seems funny in the moment is it doesn't
seem like it usually works out well in
the long run this is the age we're in
though it's like this is entertainment
though like this is the [__] i like to
look at people
real life [__] so i'm just like
why not you know what i mean and it's
just like because sometimes my life is
hectic but i just don't let people see
it but like i just been getting closer
and closer to it
to really truly not giving a [__]
to truly not giving a [__] to get to
that point right
because the thing is is that you could
you could tweet one thing that would be
that would make you way more famous for
that one thing than anything you've ever
done musically because there's so much
more of an appetite for gossip
if you said kendrick markets suck my ass
yeah i mean that's like complex
headlines it's on world starts on
everything you know it's easy and people
people know people know that you can do
that and then so people
it's just part of the game i just see it
now it's just entertainment is is a
marketing scheme no so it's just like
people are mixing real life with
like
with fake [__] like i'm not gonna lie to
you you've seen that [__] going on with
uh freddie gibbs and academics
i lowkey think that whole [__] is fake
i don't know i think there's some
reality to it but it just seems to like
well thought out to mutually beneficial
and like he's releasing the album and
it's just like this just seems like the
new age this just seems like some new
age marketing like they got together and
was like i'm just gonna go in on you you
going on me
done we get attention but i could be
completely wrong they could just
genuinely hate each other i don't
actually think that one is fake but like
you know people would always say that
during the trip you read the six nine
beef and i understood where they were
coming from even though i knew people
who were on the inside of it so i never
really thought it was fake but like i
saw what they what they meant because
you're looking at something like if
these guys are serious about wanting to
kill each other why don't they just
[__] do it it's hard for people to
wrap their head around making all these
videos and incriminating yourself and
just giving the cops a blueprint or if
anything were to happen that's that's
literally all it is like the reason i
thought it was fake is when i saw
freddie gibbs like man i could have
smoked you i was like oh this is this is
not real i could have smoked you during
your no jumper interview is what he said
oh is that what he said
yeah i mean i just i was like there's no
why would you say that yeah
that doesn't mean he was like okay he's
not gonna do that yeah
like you're letting him know like i i
have no intentions of doing it but then
now they're talking about boxing match
i'm like you guys [__] serious
that would be great that would be
entertaining it will be look it's a it's
wrestling bro it would be a good way to
culminate the storyline yeah but you
have to fight morrissey
that's like your defining beef
throughout your career right it's crazy
i don't actually have any real life i
never met i don't have any real life
smoke with the guy but um yeah it's just
kind of become a thing right because
like i took an issue with some [__] he
said and then now it's become his own
thing but yeah i would i definitely
fight him if he wanted to do he boxes
yeah man you [__] that dude wither
away if i hit him right
after i've tried to ask some of my
mexican friends if if they are even
aware of any controversy surrounding
morrissey even the idea of me bringing
it up they're like what how could you
say anything about it yeah yeah no no
it's serious for real
fame and good music will honestly do for
you yeah it gives you the benefit of the
doubt yeah you feel like that's why i
think you feel so free to tweet whatever
the [__] you want because your fans
really love your music so much that
they're just going to kind of
you could say the craziest most reckless
[__] and that kind of fits within your
character right but see i when i say
crazy reckless [__] it's it's only crazy
reckless to the outside to me i feel
like i have a point
but you know it just
i guess that's why they they they let me
do whatever because i'm never like i'm
never like
like you know when no name got on on
twitter and was like
[__] my white fans or some [__] like
that yeah i've never i've never done any
[__] like that right you know what i
mean i might say
some crazy [__] right because i mean it
at the time but i've never just come out
and be like you know what i'm just
generally feeling like [__] ali-o right
nothing specific [__] y'all what's that
like though that have to constantly kind
of bottle up and hide your hatred of
white people
[Laughter]
oh fresh off the top right there
that's a beautiful question man listen
man but okay to be fair a lot of rappers
probably do have some kind of conflicted
feeling about the fact that they have
all these white kids screaming and we're
in their face every night at the show
right um nah it does it doesn't bother
me if if you come from a certain
environment you kind of know that
you know if you have a lot of white
people at your shows if white people are
consuming your product you probably are
making money it's it's the re the reason
why there's like a demand for it is
because like white people
there's a lot of them in this country
and they have a lot of money and so if
they're giving you their money you're
probably
doing something right that's that's just
the way i've always seen it you know
like when
when that white girl jumped on stage and
said the n word on kendrick [__] like i
was like that [__] probably owns
all the vinyls that might have been the
first time that she found out she wasn't
supposed to be doing that straight up
straight up cause she was just probably
sitting in the house listening to
kendrick all day but it's just like
yeah not it it doesn't
actually bother me i think it bothers
people who like
want to be perceived a certain way they
want to be seen as like a champion to a
certain thing or like they want to be
perceived a certain way and that the
white fan base doesn't like
uh it doesn't uh what's the word i'm
looking for it doesn't like jive with
that [__] but i feel like you probably
most of your white fans are like the
self-hating white fans who like if you
said something about white people they'd
probably be like yes i agree
it's 50 50. um
i think some of them are like that and i
think the rest of them are just i don't
know what it is i have no [__] i
can't really explain it but like
i come down and talk to them after shows
and i'm just like
i can't get a read on them it's like
halfway
just super enthusiastic and they just i
think some of them just like weird music
and i probably scratch a hitch that they
can't get but i remember being a kid and
like going down the aggressive music
rabbit hole and you know i'm listening
to blink 182 and then i'm listening to
punk and and system of it
you know new metal and then death metal
and then black metal and then grind core
those are 20 20 futuristic vape pens
which you're welcome to go for these
these are edibles yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay go crazy yeah those don't
that's just nicotine yeah
oh yeah i'll try one we have we don't
mind i did i didn't bring any weave
because for some reason i
even though i've watched so many
interviews with people smoking i just
didn't bring wheat i was like i can't
smoke right no i feel you but i also
feel like a lot of people their smoking
weed personality is not as good as they
think it is
oh yeah yeah yeah they're probably just
like not that i don't think you'd have a
problem with it but i interview people
frequently where they just go quiet once
they hit the blunt and it's like what
the [__] is this you're acting like you
do this all the time dude no i'm i'm
it's obscenely talkative when i smoke
so i apologize in advance no no no but
yeah dude
i i get
i don't get questioned with that a lot
but every now and then i think people
who want to try to get under my skin
they usually come to me with this like
you got white fans you got white fans
kind of thing and it does it it
definitely doesn't
i think there's an element of it that
bothers certain people but to me i just
know what i come from and it never
really bothered me like that but um
i just understand it you know what i
mean it's not like
uh
it's not something that i sit around at
night and like keeps me up like i go on
stage and i get i get a check you know
i'm saying i get paid and then i go home
and spend that [__] so
at its very core i don't give a [__] on
that level but like it doesn't bother me
in any way because i know like yeah if
if a bunch of white people are consuming
your [__] you're probably making money i
mean you're making them not that if
[__] are consuming it you're not
making money but you know what i'm
saying i mean but they're coming to you
on your terms yeah yeah it would feel
different if you were like making music
to court them and then they're sort of
like misinterpreting you know i think
when dave chappelle left his [__]
show that was like his thing he felt
like his message was being manipulated
and he was
not you know you know he didn't
appreciate being treated this way and
being
promoted this way i mean you're
basically in charge of all that right
yeah yeah i have like control of my [__]
and i you know all that and dave
chappelle yeah he walked away from so
much money just because like it bothered
it it actually did bother him
but i don't think it was the fans it was
like the [__] in the back right yeah
yeah right but i mean at a certain point
like if you're making jokes for your
people and then you realize that there's
a shitload of people who are not your
people who are having a good old time
laughing at this i could see how that
would be
you know
not the ideal situation again
i'm just older and have more life
experience than a lot of these people so
it's just like
yeah man like sitting around and
worrying about some [__] like that would
would do nothing for you because at the
end of the day if you make it really
successful you're going to be attracting
mostly white people anyway like you go
to festivals it's
it's gonna happen there's no there's you
know what i'm saying like
unless you're a tank or a little bootsy
or some [__] you're not gonna go to an
arena and there's nothing but [__]
there you should play one of those
bootsy fests that he does i would love
to play the boosie fest you don't
understand i i
i i used to go to that [__] i went to
well like two of them
yeah man it's in it's in louisiana
fire
i was thinking about hitting them up and
just being like yo can i just slot to
one of those things i feel like i might
have the time of my life he'd probably
let you yeah yeah i mean i don't know
him personally but he'd probably let you
yeah i mean just it looks like way too
fun it's extremely fun man it's it's
it's all good it's all good vibes i
would definitely put it he probably
never let me play that but i definitely
would play that right cause like yeah um
have you thought at all about like who's
watching this like whether like do you
feel like you're speaking to your fans
or to the no jumper fans right now
um because it's a ton of two different
conversations depending on who we want
to speak to right probably no jumping
fans who probably either don't give a
[__] or just going to be like whatever
and then
but i'm i was everything i just said a
minute ago was for my fans personally
just so like so they know but yeah the
no jumping fans are like people on the
outside to probably look at this and be
like
whatever [__] you just you just like
white people or some [__] but you just
wanted to talk to another white person
you just wanted to talk to another white
person you [__] ass [__] collecting
white people
um
because yeah like i'm kind of like
paranoid about like talking about like
[__] that i know you've already probably
covered in interviews and stuff man
i don't [__] care cuz like the
military thing is particularly
interesting to me like when i said i was
watching this white guy with glasses
make a video about you he was talking
about how your your time in the military
may have uh influenced some of the
production on these records
the loud clanking and the fighting in
the background i'm like that's quite a
inference like that's a stretch he does
he doesn't know like when you join the
military you
take a test and you have to pick a job
and they give you a job actually so like
depending on your job
you will be fighting or doing this and
that but he doesn't [__] know me he's
never met me and he doesn't know what i
did in the military he doesn't know how
long i was and he doesn't know where i
was right so him saying that is just he
saw i was in the military was like
military bombs war right this is why his
music's loud it's so
childish you know what i'm saying it's
just it's a very surface level right
it's the most surface level [__] you
could possibly but it
this kind of [__] happens to me a lot
and i don't
respond to any of it because it's
pointless you know but like yeah you
asking me right now yeah that's
literally how it happens it happens all
the time but when when i first got in
here people were you know that you know
death grips yeah yeah people were
comparing me to death i knew they would
even before i did anything i knew they
would so i tried to get ahead of it
right and
they still did it anyway because we're
both loud and black and have a beard and
i just knew people would just
put that [__] together yeah when i was
reading random [__] uh to get ready to
interview you i just kept seeing them
compare your deaf girl so so many times
i had to go back and like listen to them
again because it's been so many years
and i'm like oh okay this is not really
that similar but they want to put it in
the same box it's just it's
it's surface level [__] it's i said this
years ago but like it's no offense to
them but the kind of [__] i talk about
just
taking the perception of me out of it me
talking about race this and that blah
blah blah you compare me
talking about black people issues on wax
to a band with dicks on their cover
it's not even in the same tax bracket
but yet we're smooshed together just
because like we might both be loud just
because some people just aren't smart
enough to get the nuance of it and it's
just like
what can you actually do with that other
than just laugh at it and
try to get ahead i got to get ahead of
you do you have a relationship with them
though or is that just some other [__]
that you have nothing to do with i i
have i have no relationship with them i
never met that i have no issue with them
i just like
don't like to be compared to people just
strictly because i'm black and
you know some of these fans don't know
any black people right they're just like
oh [__] two black people that do similar
things
there can only be one it's like no
[__] so you don't have like high
hopes for there being like an
avant-garde like hip-hop revolution or
anything like that i no i do i would
love that right
i would welcome that i was actually
tweeting about that [__]
the way that
mainstream artists like you look on um
[Music]
any album look at a little baby album
it's the same features dirt
et future
et cetera there's a reason for that they
stick together they come up they make
money together they know that like all
them on the song regardless of what that
should sound like it's gonna go you're
gonna spread it around spotify you know
what i'm saying there's an element of
that in the underground with like guys
like me earl danny brown right i want to
like
i would love to like mush that together
because we would all come up it would be
like we're all like hunkering down in
our little world instead of like
we're just weirdos on the outside of
mainstream and we you know it's it we we
have our own thing going on and a lot of
people decry what we do so like i think
it's it's important that we like we need
a union
like the way that they have these like
90s rapper tours still i've been doing a
couple of those and it's like it's a
great vibe and it's cool to see them
like they play venues that are way
[__] bigger than they would be able
to play on their own when you stick ice
cube and dj quick and snoop and game all
on the same tour or whatever people want
to come out you see the same thing with
like the [__] psychopathic records
type era there's all these like juggalo
style rappers even if they're not
directly associated with icp and that's
its own solving the same like related
artists things you need your up and
smoke tour
yo that would be great that would be
incredible like yo i saw a flyer
like months ago i had like baby bash yin
yang twins wow like trip that's all
these people in that i was like oh my
god the old [__] in me was just like
yes yeah and i just wanted to go to it
this i want to harness the energy for
the underground yeah yeah but yeah
unionizing is a different thing now that
that would involve rappers getting along
with each other right on a widespread
scale it's hard to imagine no i was
standing on the stage for a moment i'm
watching the people who are you know
turning up to exhibit or game or
whatever the [__] it was and i'm looking
out into the audience and it's all like
dudes with their shirts tucked in and
like they look like they have you know
good solid jobs they're like 48 they're
standing with their wife
and they're just loving
dog or game or whatever and it's like
this is complete the average age here is
literally twice the average age at the
average show that i would go to a
thousand percent that they're um they're
living out their
uh
whatever you their youth you know what i
mean they're just going back to that
[__] but they got the money to come and
come out
and they will support you when they see
people like all those like acts
all in one thing they're just like yes i
want to be there it makes you feel like
you're one of you um i'm missing out on
something yeah brings you back to that
that place
when you think about your your
biggest influences rap wise when you're
a child what comes to mind or even just
musically in general
um when i was a child um
so when i was really young
um
i wasn't into music at all like when i
was really young
the first
song i really liked the song first music
i ever liked was [__] handsome
you remember oomba that makes me feel
like we're the exact same age because
when i was like 12 or 13 that was the
most popular song in the [__] world
yeah i thought one of them was a girl
i did too i thought they were both girls
i thought it was a group of women
i really did i thought like
but yeah no you know
that
the first i didn't know anything about
music so i didn't have any context of
like oh this is hanson only certain
types of people listen to this but i
just like that [__] and i was like i
need that [__] so that's the first thing
i remember liking somehow from there i
started listening to a bunch of random
[__] and i found my way to cameron i
don't really know how wow but come like
camron um diplomats
um
yeah those are the first like rappers
those are like probably my
base influence like a lot of east coast
[__] right a-z
a lot of like hardcore hip-hop
cameron blew my [__] mind into a
million pieces when i was like you know
18 or 19 when i first heard him because
it was just like i i didn't know you
know i'm coming off of being the biggest
g-unit fan in the world and it's like i
didn't know that against a rapper got to
be this irreverent and funny and silly
and have so many references it was just
like the polar [__] opposite of what
50 was doing yeah and i was just blown
away and
that's what i like about cameron like i
was born in new york and like when you
come from like whatever kind of
environment you
just no smiles no waste no that yeah i
like that cameron still kept like a
sense of humor but he was serious about
his [__] like he never he was you can't
play him he's not a goof right but he he
can joke around like if you watch that
[__] killer season movie that [__] is
funny as [__] he just spits on a little
girl yeah he just straight up spits on
her that was a real moment for a lot of
people like can i laugh at this can i
approve of this like he just spit on her
you know it just it didn't have any he
didn't have to do it he just put it in
there but like his own movie in his own
movie
that he has complete control of
but yeah he he's a funny dude um but
yeah uh i i liked that about him i think
and i think that came out with his raps
even like him rapping over the soul
samples and [__] right they were just
weird to me yeah so that drew me in the
production and like his his rhymes and
all that [__] like he was rapping all
whimsical yeah we pulled up the lyrics
to suck it or not the other day and i
was like doing like spoken word reading
of that and like just the fact that he
said like oh you don't like men me
neither what a cowinky think
when i saw that i'm like reading that
just thinking like i might have gone my
whole life
never even thinking that a rapper knew
about the existence of cowinky
dinky
and i don't know where i know about that
from i'm sure i heard my mom say it as a
kid for sure man he
i actually forgot that song exists and i
forgot that's
he like uh
i know it's but here comes the hot sauce
he like dropped the beetle no no
he invented paws and no
yeah man cameron one of my favorites one
of my goats right definitely
um man i got so many good things written
down that i could just randomly bring
out what do you think of the second
amendment
you rap about you know actual second
event yeah about guns from time to time
what are your thoughts on like the
legalization i personally in my part the
legalization of it oh damn you you gave
me like a cnn question
i'm just interested in what your
thoughts are on it overall
all right so
this is so personally
i personally think every single black
person
in this country should have some sort of
baseline knowledge of weaponry or like
uh or shooting or have somebody should
in their house should have a license or
something that's just me personally and
the reason is because i think that
we get shot in the street so much and so
much random [__] just happens to black
people all the time we got to be armed i
think personally and me personally
i think i love guns i think i own guns i
got them legally i have a concealed
carry and like
i just
it's for defense you know it makes me
feel better like when i'm just like
doing my day-to-day [__] but
i think that it just should be harder to
get that's all i don't really think
there should be like a widespread ban on
them because people just want to get rid
of them all together right and i don't
think that's realistic you're not
hundreds of millions of guns in this
country yeah hundreds and you know like
what are they gonna do and
i would dare say most of them are not
registered at all you know what i'm
saying so you're never really gonna get
rid of the guns in in america which you
can do is just make it harder it's way
too easy to get a gun yeah i'll just be
honest about that so that's that's it i
was listening to a podcast the other day
with this liberal commentator saying
that
so many of his liberal democratic
friends are buying guns right now
because their viewpoint is that they
don't want the republicans to have all
the guns if some [__] goes down which
seems like a pretty reasonable they
already have them like yeah all these
these crazy militias and [__] they've
been had guns since before any of us was
thinking about about that [__] since
before i was born
they got bunkers man they got [__]
rice and [__] stuffed up they got dried
up food they're ready to go so it's like
you you're trying to trying to play
catch up in 2021 to these kind of people
is not going to be possible but like
i just that's great that people are
waking up to it now because i know a lot
of people are just like nah no guns i
don't like guns blah blah but i really
think it should just be harder to get
them
instead of it just being like
it's just too easy that's all it's just
way too simple to get them in easy and
if it was just like harder screening
like
more like things to like detect these
crazy ass people who actually go out and
do crazy [__] with them it would be a
lot better but i don't think there needs
to be a widespread ban on them that's
not that's just my opinion though
personally as an owner personally that's
my opinion but um it's crazy when you
see people who are really immersed in
like gun culture like this [__] kid
who shot up at school the other day and
then they're showing his parents buying
him the gun they're displaying it on
social media the mom so he gets caught
looking at ammunition in class on his
phone and the teacher tells his mom and
then his mom doesn't even respond hears
the voicemail and texts her son and says
you need to get better at not getting
caught
that was a wild moment for me
am i really reading this like is this
really how this went down and granted
they got charged with manslaughter which
i guess is nice uh
yeah they they they had to because like
that
then negligence is literally what led to
that because they could have stopped
that so many times i i was looking at
that [__] too like they
what what happened like the kid they
caught the kid in school doing some [__]
like drawing some crazy [__] and they
called the parents they let him go back
to class and then he started shooting
everybody
it's like it could have been stopped at
so many levels and it could have been
stopped at a parenting level but the
parents were just shitty parents really
and they were just like whatever and
it's just like if you're going to be
obsessed with guns or whatever that's
cool but like you can't
just
because of your negligence like yeah all
these kids died because of your kid not
your asses in jail
so it's just like all you had to do was
not everything you did
yeah like they really managed to [__] up
every last thing that you could have
potentially done that they did
everything wrong like down to the day of
it happening they did everything wrong
so it's just like when i was 16 i was in
a photography class and i took a picture
of a
dead squirrel like that had been run
over by a car
and then it's getting developed and the
teacher sees that i'm taking a picture
of this dead animal and i've come to
learn that uh torturing animals is like
one of the biggest signs that somebody's
going to become a killer yeah it's like
it's kind of a sociopath yeah so they
reported me i had to go to the office
they're doing all kinds of you know
they're making me do all these reviews
and stuff and i'm like do you think that
i actually ran a [__] squirrel over
with my car even if i wanted to do that
nobody could do that unless you trapped
it and held it in place yeah you'd have
to really be like you'd have to sit
outside all day and like keep attempting
that yeah just drive up and down the
street all day until you merge something
that would be like content and but that
was
1999 or something and that was how
concerned they were about that and then
when i hear that story about that kid
i'm just like like
these yo
it's just dumb ass it's like the the the
people you saw that were crazy and
stupid when we were younger they grow up
and have kids i'm realizing that now as
i get older i'm like oh you don't get
smarter right like if you if you're dumb
right now and you're crazy as [__] and
don't got your [__] together when you're
40 or 50 and you're having kids you just
pass that [__] down so like
your parents are crazy that is what's
scary it's crazy you see a lot of [__]
these days and it's like jesus christ
you're passing that down to your kids
like i know a girl who's fully into
queuing on and she just had a baby and
i'm just like hell yeah that seems like
you're just legitimately abusing your
child because of the fact that you're
gonna one day tell him that that's how
the world works
that's scary
i mean bro
that q anon [__] is just hilarious to me
yeah because it's just because you have
a little bit of a right-wing media
obsession right would you characterize
an obsession or just a fringe it's not
really
i guess it is kind of an obsession i
just find it interesting yeah cause
they're so crazy like
and nothing they does me like all they
do
is
the only thing they're looking out for
is themselves and they'll say anything
to support that so their views and
everything just shift depending on the
situation right and just as somebody
who's seen it for years just watching it
just straight up entertaining right i'm
not gonna lie it's just entertaining so
it's always been like that as soon as i
could even change the tv channel when
i'm thinking when i was like 18 and i
moved out of the house i was watching
like bill o'reilly and [__] because it
was way more interesting cameron was a
[__] bill o'reilly like i know you
doggy i got like you mad it's classic
like it it
i i said this to somebody before but i
showed them like two like political
analysts arguing and then i showed them
like one of six nine's instagram lives
and i said tell me the difference better
audio
literally six dollars will have better
audio but it's like there's no actual
difference it's the same [__] so that's
what that's what i get out of it it's
like [__] from like business people
who are pretending to not be like ghetto
yeah
it's a weird world is there anybody that
you that you particularly like in that
world that you sort of hate watch or
that you just find particularly
fascinating um
i used to hate watch alec jones alex
jones but i stopped hate watching him
because he became kind of entertaining
like i started like kind of liking it
not what he was saying but i was like
looking forward to him i was like yo
this dude is out of his mind he's always
selling like
crazy [__] like soap it's like a
futuristic soap that'll keep you keep
the the liberals off you well i mean but
he got canceled by youtube and
everywhere else so he kind of has to
cancel well yeah they took away his
youtube channel and [__] so yeah and
twitter and everything so really he kind
of has to sell these products like
there's no he's not gonna be able to get
advertising from almost any brand he
kind of has to sell his own vitamins he
got real life canceled then yeah
[__] they got his ass um i guess
i don't really like watching him but i
guess tucker calls on some [__] yeah but
i just i just see him on twitter i don't
like watch a show i go through phases
with these guys where like i i had like
a month of ben shapiro and then i just
felt like i'd seen it all and that i
wasn't learning anything about his
worldview that i got it and then i just
kind of moved on i'd love to debate that
guy man because he's just like he's not
he
it's like
his his viewpoints are just
they have just enough [__] that makes it
make enough sense so that someone stupid
can think it's genius right so it's just
like he just needs to be put in front of
someone who concedes past that do you
ever think that black people will
embrace the republican party
sometimes i wonder if it's on the way
because you see the mexicans support the
republican party like crazy in america i
think that black people will get tired
of getting [__] over by the democrats
at some point i don't know if that'll i
don't know if that'll
shift to republicans because republicans
are just
a lot of republicans are just more
outright racist so like it's it
it would be harder for black people to
jive with like
but i feel like the vast majority of
modern republicans if somebody seems
like they're on their side they will
welcome men like candace owens doesn't
seem like she's having any trouble
getting accepted in this world even
though she's way more far gone than a
lot of these people i think she's gonna
be your president one day bro i really
do but um
yeah i don't think so i don't think
black people ever embrace but who knows
they did at one point back in the day
but it was different like i saw a thing
the other day that said that
two percent of uh hispanic people like
being called latinx
that to me just really made me feel like
you the democrats are not knowing their
audience right now
no man they
no
it's like it they they just don't and um
there's no way to they're so
disconnected from what's actually going
on it's actually funny to watch
sometimes so like
it's like you want them to be to do the
right thing it's like you want them to
like
be better but they just don't know how
it's like joe biden is
9 700 years old there's no way he can
connect with anything going on but he'll
say he will yeah you know he was at
roscoe's
before [__]
before uh the election he's not at
roscoe's now
he's a good point and he won't be back
and he doesn't have he doesn't
nothing
that's going on with black people
concerns him at the moment when's the
last time he went to roscoe's
right before the election he was at
roscoe's to see him
no i didn't go to see him he was just
like what's up it's me joe i'm at
roscoe's just casually i go here all the
time yeah this is my usual spot and then
he was on the breakfast club he did he
did all the urban [__] yeah and joe
rogan wouldn't have him on
he said no which i thought was pretty
funny not urban enough for him he had uh
but he didn't have trump either he had
bernie sanders on
really yeah that's kind of weird that's
like the extreme version of okay i mean
i mean i feel like the more extreme left
or right you get you get
similar plane i don't know much about
him you know i don't really watch him
like joe rogan yeah people think i watch
him but i don't i don't have anything
against him i just know he's like the
reason why i started podcasting but the
older i get the more and more i feel
like i'm listening to my old-ass grandpa
just like talk about [__] and it
just isn't really the same
like when i saw him ask snoop dogg if
the west coast east coast beef was still
alive that that
kind of summed it up for me wait he
asked him that yeah when
like a a couple weeks ago i just saw the
clip i didn't watch the whole thing
that's what's up and when i see that i
feel like it must be amazing to be able
to do interviews where they have no
expectation of you knowing what the [__]
is going on yeah man i can't believe you
actually asked him that in real time
yeah that's tight i gotta i gotta go
watch that [__] yeah but but like
somehow his character you know we talk
about like character like your fans
expect certain things from you nobody
expects joe rogan to not ask that
question so he just gets to ask that
question you know i mean you could you
can literally find that out with a quick
google search and be like nah but it's
just like you know and it's been like 25
years it's
shout out joe rogan though because i
think he's he's also five nine so shout
out to him that's i shout out everyone
five minutes really
royce the five nine if it wasn't for him
you could have ended up adding that to
your name maybe
[Laughter]
maybe so is that why his name is roasted
five nine man
yeah that's what's up
pretty solid um switching gears
what or who influenced your stage
presence when i was watching you perform
this is one thing i was thinking about
and never see rappers do this kind of
thing on stage so i'm wondering like who
you felt like actually influenced that
um
a couple people um
the first one is someone you you
definitely don't know it's a guy from
baltimore his name is abdulli okay this
is probably my main influence is because
when i first came to baltimore i went to
a warehouse show and i saw abdu
performing to like
30 people maybe i was one of them
he was just
playing his songs off a laptop and just
going in the crowd and performing i'd
never seen anything like that in my life
so like
i started hanging out with him and i
started adopting his style and i evolved
into what i have now so that's my main
influence but um other than that the guy
from uh
uh the main singer from bad brains oh
man yeah
as soon as you start talking about the
other dude i started thinking in my head
i wonder how influenced it was by bad
brains because to me they're like the
most ahead of their time banned maybe
ever
yeah they were way too ahead of their
time like crazy on so many levels yeah
um bad brains uh this band called fear
you know um fear um just a lot of punk
artists black flag people like that
because they um
you know look at their shows it's hectic
they're like they're out there the
vocals might sound like [__] they might
[__] up
but the live element is what i want
people to take from it i'm going out
there there's no backing track there's
nothing i'm going out there and i'm
gonna give it 100 if i [__] up if i run
out of breath you're just gonna hear it
right so like it might not be the most
beautiful sounding thing but like i'm
going out there and giving you a hundred
percent because like yeah these are the
guys when i watched them they were
always doing that i'm not you'll never
see me up there with like a a crazy
outfit just walking around just kind of
like i just don't operate like that
right so yeah is there a time where you
want to perform like that you're on tour
you're kind of under the weather and
you're like i want to do the gucci mane
thing and just walk back and forth with
my finger in the air see no see
yeah a lot actually i do because it's
tiring but the thing with like gucci
mane the reason why it works with him
because he has his authenticity and who
he is backs that so he can go up there
he doesn't have to do what i do right
you know what i mean i go out there like
i'm trying to prove myself you know what
i mean so that's one of the things cause
it's not i don't have none against
people who do that [__] because i love
i've been to a gucci mane show and i
love it
even though he performs nothing like
it's very him
it's very him it's like the one i went
to was years ago it was a billion [__]
on stage and it was just like it was
just him he had just a song playing and
everybody was rocking everybody was
drunk it was like it was a good ass time
you know what i'm saying i'm not going
there expecting him to do what i do
right but people come to my [__]
expecting me to do that so like i have
to live up to that and like yeah that's
just bad brains and like punk artists
and when i was in baltimore i performed
a lot of hardcore artists so like this
is why i perform the way i do you're
like welcomed into that scene
yeah
and and it's not cause like i wasn't
trying to be in that scene i think just
the way i was performing just kind of
meshed with them better
than it did like uh
you know a street rap scene or something
like that you ever met donald trump
and yes whenever anyone mentions ball
tomorrow i have to ask them something
for donald trump this is becoming a meme
on the show
no but i remember like
a lot of people were excited when she
said she moved to baltimore
that's so crazy you brought up yeah she
i think she lives in baltimore she does
yeah she uh oh yeah she's probably not
from there right but i've i've seen so
many videos of her just getting in
arguments with random girls because she
really likes like
dudes like trapper ass dudes like she
doesn't want to live out here she got
like locked up for like weed or
something right i think she was being a
drug mule for somebody or trafficking
packs for somebody i believe yeah damn
she did the time too that's some real
[__] listen
she came to my kids one year birthday
party really yeah
she was well behaved don't get any ideas
guys
no i don't know tiana trump no i'd love
to meet her
does um
just given your name how would how would
you rate your level of interest in nfts
i don't know [__] about nsts dude okay
um
it's just it
i wish i did but everyone keeps coming
to me being like yo you should do an nft
your jpeg mafia right you need to do an
nft so i'm i'm gonna have to learn about
it but i don't know anything about i
know surface level [__] that's it i
don't know anything about i think your
fans will get behind it
they might you just have to make it as
obnoxious as possible like just really
not tailor it to anything that they
would actually want to make it your own
thing i don't know what it would look
like but it's got to be there's got to
be like a real [__] vibe to it if
like i'm just going to do what i want
here it has to be like something digital
right yeah
do i have too much [__] that could
that could fit that do you make art in
any other forms visually or is it just
rap the only thing i'm good at is music
really i have no
i have vague other interests like i like
certain other things but music is my
main
like thing i don't really like
like to do anything else right like so
yeah no i don't
as far as other art i might dabble in it
but music is really like where i put my
time i was with a dude playing poker
last night who was a pro baseball player
and somebody asked him about how he
ended up being a baseball player that
like you know you played as a little kid
excited he's like yeah it's pretty much
all i did my entire life and i was just
thinking like
that sounds so
easy and simple if you just found this
one thing that you liked when you were
like five and you just kept doing it
that's it became a professional made a
shitload of money and never even had to
really consider like going another path
because for me i just feel like
anything i become interested in there's
there's a shelf life where it's just at
some point i'm going to become
interested in something else or my
interest levels are going to wane i'm
always going to be pulled in a different
direction
i
i don't know why i don't have that i
just um
music caught on to me like mad early and
i never i never had any interest in
anything else i ca i can't even remember
there's things i've wanted to do here
and there
but i've never ever wanted to actually
do anything else seriously like i never
actually like put down like time and
effort to like researching things like i
do with music right
for sure
um
do you [__] with peggy hill
peggy hill from king of the hill
yeah
i do that's like my favorite character
on any
cartoon ever i just started one i never
watched that show before and i just
started watching it really funny as [__]
it's actually i don't know why i
actually didn't wasn't watching it
before that's my happy place like if i
have a caterpillar if i'm stressed out
or whatever and it's like if i have like
20 minutes before i go to bed i'm
putting on king of the hill and it just
sort of grounds me or something and i've
spent very little time in the american
south but something about it just really
just feels very pure
it's like it's very
rednecky and white trashy yeah and those
are things i
thoroughly enjoy so
i definitely grew up white trash but i
just didn't grow up around rednecks so
it does feel kind of foreign to me a lot
of it brown rednecks yeah and and white
trash i grew up around straight juggalo
ass [__] not grew up around it
but there was no actually i didn't grow
up around them
my teenage years were spent around these
a lot of these types that's what i was
to say yeah from the state that i grew
up in there was at one point like a gang
a federal gang
shutdown of a juggalo gang
yeah because this guy is a real guest
the frats and the juggalos were going to
war in this one uh area like the frat
boys and the juggles had a huge beef
they were actually like warring like
damn and it only freaks me out too
because it happened in this area called
keen and when i graduated high school my
parents convinced me to go to one
college to tour it to see what i thought
of it and before i was just like i'm not
like i can't do this and then and it was
there so i know where this battle took
place
you're saying it like it's a civil war
it's like this battle like they showed
up with like swords and [__] and they
just went to war i wonder if i had been
living there who i would have cited
because you know i don't like now i feel
like i could really vibe with the
juggalos but yeah i [__] with the g i
[__] with juggle though some people
don't like him but
every time i meet a juggle they're
always like really nice and
not really concerned with anything but
insane clown posse so i don't really see
a problem they definitely don't have the
elitist gene not at all dude they're
just like
bumping icp and going about the business
yeah so like but what's crazy is i just
interviewed violin jay and he's kind of
going through some health problems and
stuff and uh they're like slowing down a
lot
with the touring and that that was
really weird for me to realize like oh
they're slowing down return but there
will be a day where icp no longer exists
yeah i have never really known a world
well i guess i did but i was like 12
when i found out about icp so i've never
really had to imagine a world without
them as an adult
well
that's happening man getting older and
everything we loved before is fading
away that's just the way it is i've
started to notice [__] like that too i'm
just like
i've just gotten desensitized to it i
guess yeah bob dole's dead
yeah that [__] was crazy it's like
i don't even i don't even know why i
laughed at that but like i just know i
remember i was a kid like being fully
convinced that this guy was a terrible
dude and clinton was the best and i'm
rooting for clinton i don't know why but
because clinton was like cooler
he played sax it's so crazy that's what
got him over like we both immediately
thought of the saxophone sax bro like he
played sax and it just like
he got the benefit of the doubt for
[__] for years [__] [__] those war
crimes that guy could play a meme
just like that's all it took as crazy as
[__] it was the context too cause he's
he's there with arsenio hall yeah i see
he's on that he's on our side and he was
like arsenio was like the show the urban
show at the time and like yeah but
that's all it took is yo joe but when i
told you the joe biden and the roscoe
[__] that's what he was trying to do he
was trying to like create a sax moment
but it's just it's
you know
i don't think
from my perspective i don't think any
love was lost for bill clinton when he
got some top in the oval office
that was a legendary [__] what an
[__]
look back at the um
looking back i don't know comedians and
whatever late night shows and [__] back
at the time they were they were with it
they were like
come on man he just got you know what i
mean like nobody nobody was actually mad
at it right
it's kind of astounding that trump
didn't have anything like that because i
feel like that's that's way more of a
him thing probably just better at hiding
it yeah definitely probably just way
better at hiding it we still don't
really know what what's going on with
the the epstein's girl case because
apparently trump keeps getting
implicated in that but i haven't really
heard too much yeah every time i every
time i look at it it's like somebody
somebody and trump and i'm just like man
this dude is popping up way more than i
thought he would right but you know he's
just better at hiding it he's on that
plane
yo
they were out there on that plane
[__] smokey was on that [__] too oh
yeah yeah i saw that
um
okay
this was a a bar that i just felt like i
needed to write down and just throw out
there
covered in money they think and i strip
my pops was a ghost and my partners
ain't [__] yep
what was going through your head when
you wrote that that really stood out to
me
so covered in money they thinking i
straight
pause of course
i'm just i'm just i'm just playing with
the idea that like
you know i just came up with some money
[__] must be thinking i'm stripping i
was just playing around really but like
the second part yeah my pops was never
it's just a it's a it's like a way of
saying like my father wasn't around and
a lot of my partners can't be trusted
that's basically what i was just pre i
was just portraying paranoia i guess but
do you feel that way like the a lot of
the people that you grew up around and
stuff that you can't necessarily have
the same kind of trust that you might
have had before
um i have people that's been in my life
for a long time that i still trust and
i'm still around but there's some people
that i've met along the way that yeah
their their entire perception of me is
switched up maybe due to like my what i
do or like just something random
but yeah that's kind of where it came
from just like having people i thought i
could trust like
you know
do something to betray that and i just i
just kind of wrapped it up without being
specific right
i like it this is another one i wrote
down what you got
i only rap out of spite yeah loss is the
theme of my life hell yeah
[Music]
these these are good this is this is
also true
this is me being a nerd sitting at home
listening to the album and reading
through it on rap genius at the same
time because it's hard to make out some
of it oh my god that [__] hate that
site um they they [__] my lyrics up so
much
and you know all these like little
critics and stuff this is where they get
all their information from they don't
actually look into anything so they just
rap genius real quick so some [__]
is there it's like
it becomes fact and i'm just like if we
were selling the cd era would you be
putting
your full lyrics in the cd booklets like
bands sometimes do yeah yeah i love that
[__] i used to love that [__] i'm still
yeah i come from that era so like i i
still do that in some form i put my
lyrics up and all that [__] right um
what was the bar it was a i only rap out
it's the truth man i'm a producer first
um when i rap it's only out of some
motivation and it's usually to spite
somebody or something so like if you
actually listen to what i'm saying you
can hear it like very clearly but it's
like it's very rare
i'm not the type of guy to sit around
and just be rapping for fun like i'd
make music for fun but like um
yeah that's what that means is literal
like i rap out of spite basically do you
feel like rapping out of spite do you
feel like you need to have some sort of
like outside motivation aside from just
i want to make money and i want to be
famous yes
where do you find it
spite
because because otherwise i'll just make
beats and i won't i won't have anything
to say really because like
i like to keep a lot of things private
i i'm not
that level of a rapper where i can play
around with personal [__]
that heavily sometimes i can but for the
most part i can't so if i'm rapping i
got to be motivated by something i'm not
just on here just like spitting for
nothing it's kind of like that i feel
like a like a hitman with it it's like
i'm only going out when i need to really
right but like as far as like making
beats and producing i do that every day
i was doing that before i got here
really
and it'll go all night
maybe not but like i just
the point is i just enjoy doing it you
know what i mean like um
like do you like do you enjoy doing this
yeah there's a there's a party that like
likes doing this [__] yeah i like it a
lot exactly otherwise you wouldn't be
doing it yeah i i just i just like
making beats the
everything else recording
the other stuff i need to be motivated
and then i can like it otherwise like i
don't really find a reason to i know
that sounds weird but that's just how i
think i feel like my my life ends up
divided into two things which is
basically like creating and then just
taking things in you know like very very
massively different segments of my brain
between
doing an interview and
watching other interviews with that
person or listening to that person's
albums or watching a documentary and
then actually doing something with a
person that i found out about in the
documentary those are two such polar
things
and it's interesting so like let's say
you had like a couple hours before bed
yeah
or are you more likely to like make
beats than go on netflix and like what
what what mood is more beneficial to
either
this is what i do i get on netflix
and i watch something i sit down and
tell myself i'm going to watch this and
something and it'll motivate me to just
go work really i just like do it i just
i just enjoy
working it's that addictive to me it is
i i don't want to you know it's it
yeah it is it's just it it sounds like
how it is
yeah that says a lot though about it
being that much of a draw to you you
know yeah i love it i love it there's
nothing else that like gives me
motivation more but yeah the the rapping
part i like rapping and i appreciate
like good rapper or good rappers that's
why i [__] with like denzel and people
like that right like
me personally
i didn't grow up just like wanting to be
a rapper right i was always wanting to
be a producer first the rapping came
because i felt like i had some [__] to
say i wanted to say some [__]
and i did
but like yeah i'm not gonna rap unless i
have something to say
how'd you meet denzo
he
hit me up
on
twitter just [__] with the music yeah
he was just [__] with the music he
wrote a song i have called manpurse and
he was like i love this [__]
and he um he wanted me to be on this
song
uh vengeance with me and zillakami right
it ended up with zilliqami at first it
was just me and him right and um yeah
that's that's how i met i got on the
song and it's funny because he actually
sent the song back and he was like
i don't know about this one big dog yeah
i was like okay whatever i was just
gonna put the verse on something else
but then he hit me back like a week
later and he was like actually yeah
we're gonna go with it and zillow
commies on it now and i was like wow
that's better than i thought i was it
was that's great
he really is an incredible talent he's
probably one of the best rappers i've
seen in real life yeah yeah and he
doesn't write anything down he
freestyles that [__] which is even
freakier so like yeah he's actually like
that it's crazy because he was right
there for the whole space shows perp
thing the x-ray citation wave the
tour with billy eilidge he went to
school with trayvon martin too wow i did
not know that that's crazy yeah
something like that like he he's he's
been he's been like in the middle or
like not involved directly but like in
the midst of some serious [__] before
like yeah x was staying at his house
yeah um that's the first time i heard x
was them dissing space goes together
yeah the space goes [__] [__] yeah
that's crazy man yeah his that that era
was really interesting didn't he like
tattoo something he like tattooed space
goes perp
like [__] purp on his like risk or
something that's when you're really
living in the moment when you hate
somebody so much again
you tattoo [__] this [__] on your wrist
that's amazing
that's actually great uh but yeah um
that's there's nothing like that's
teenage adolescent aggression right
there because
and actually to be honest i know a ton
of people have [__] gangs whacked out
all over their [__] arms and [__] too
so i'm probably got around the same age
yeah it's really it's really not any
really different when you really think
about it but yeah he's he's been and
he's been kind of around a lot of
serious [__] yeah so yeah and also
bro
this is just random and [__] but i
didn't realize he's he's younger than i
thought thought he was yeah yeah every
time i talk to him i'm just forget that
he's
not the same age as me
i've been listen i feel like i've been
listening for like 10 years was he's
late 2025 oh really yeah holy [__]
exactly right
i feel like i've known about him for
yeah nearly 10 years it's like what the
[__] he has to been rap he had to like
drop that raider straight from my
raiders yeah when he was like 14 or
something i've just seen so many like
scenes go by and then he always kind of
seems like he's the last one left that's
still doing his thing out of those
scenes
maybe not the last but you know
yeah like
like one of the last of a dying breed
from that era yeah yeah
for sure i mean
what else
uh
space go space goes perp
he called me a [__] on twitter one time
i feel like almost everyone has gotten
some bars from him at some point yeah
hell yeah i was nobody at the time
though so i i felt really like anointed
yeah i was posting pictures of like my
family or something on my twitter and
he's like get this bitch-ass [__] off my
timeline and i was like hell yeah i just
retweeted it
[Laughter]
wow [__] was great
i feel like it's one of like my biggest
influences musically so i feel like you
could take on his persona if you wanted
oh oh perp just to be like more of a
troll darker with it and like
people would just kind of let you rock
like that
you know what when i get really old and
i actually when i just completely fall
off i can't make any more money i'll
probably just go at that route i'm just
like i seen him beefing with all of new
york the other day
yeah he's just like [__] new york he's
been leading on twitter so many times i
can never i don't even know if it's i
don't even know if it's him anymore i
just
every now and then i'll catch one of
those i'm just like you know what man i
respect that you're consistent with this
[__] so yeah maybe i'll maybe i'll um
take the mantle from him like candyman
or something every time i see like a
screenshot sgp tweet
i wonder it's like the way like i love
when they bring back all the hack tweets
from all the rappers like when offset
said balls in my face
that's my favorite one yeah i love i
love it um young thug smoking penises
oh no he said that
we we smoking penises oh he really said
that yeah cause that was way back in the
day and then he finally deleted the
tweet like four or five years later
after people kept retweeting it
that's crazy he really tweeted i always
thought it was fake no that's so tough i
remember it
smoking penises
that's my biggest regret is that i've
never asked them about that on camera
you should you know yeah
that's so strange
all right yeah that's great smoking
penises i want to get that tattooed like
on my back he tweeted that [__] like 10
years ago or something too like or some
[__] like that those are rapper names
smoking penises
that's like some soundcloud
yeah yeah time would have passed um you
got anything you're pushing at this
point or like you dropped a bunch of
projects this year right yeah i dropped
um
i dropped the ep while i was extremely
upset at a bunch of people and then i
dropped the
lp last um on my birthday which is
october right and that was the last
album of my contract so
i'm free now who are you signed with
republic okay and that was a bad
experience overall or no my experience
with the republic was fantastic i
actually um had to be
on republic because the label before
that was
[__] garbage so that's what was a bad
situation okay so um but yeah now i'm
off that whole situation you're ready to
be independent or you feel like you need
a label
[__] no man i was basically into like
all the [__] i was doing was just on my
own doing like they just i wanted to be
independent because they were just in
the way like
everything i've been doing i just i'm
just doing it like they
didn't really do much they weren't
spending money on advertising they
weren't like pushing things like
they weren't really doing press like
that it's like i basically was
independent yeah i was just under the
mantle of a label so i just wanted to
get off of it so
nobody could tell me like because i just
i like to drop [__] randomly sometimes
and they were always on some like it
needs to be on a playlist you need to do
this and that and i'm just like [__]
no like nobody [__] k like
imagine
you remember like story of added on
yeah the [__] the drake this yeah
imagine if he wanted to put that out
right right but someone told him wait
it needs to go on this playlist right it
wouldn't have hit the same correct yeah
it's timing or the kendrick's control
[__] it's timing and everything it's
just like
you can't do [__] like that and also i'm
not the type of artist who's like no
one's gonna hear my [__] on some like
super duper curated like popular
playlist and be like whoa what's that
they're just gonna be like what the [__]
is this get it away from me right i'm
not the type of thing that's gonna get
attracted from playlist people are just
gonna find me you've never had that
experience where you get put on some
playlist of like maybe more experimental
stuff or whatever and you actually saw
the bump where you got a bunch of fans
from it no i cuz i look at because i
look at raw numbers you know like i do i
don't i don't do none of this like
play play like oh i'm more popular now
i'm like no how much more it's literally
so like i look at the raw numbers and no
i don't get a bump i see the [__] i get
a bump from and it's not any of those
playlist shits it's it's like you you
you get some plays from it but it's not
enough to
warrant like making a fuss out of you
know what i'm saying but like um
the things that actually
the place my numbers come from is just
literally word of mouth or just people
finding me on their own like as as crazy
as that sounds like
that's just it it's actually just
organic so like
there's no point in that it needs to be
things need to happen in the moment
because it's going to spread if it's
going to spread word of mouth it needs
to spread like fast and it doesn't need
to be staggered like that but anyway
yeah my bad i was i was talking to you
like you work for me no no but i get it
though for sure it's cool to know that
you know that and it's just it feels
like you are like an artist who
i feel like you're talking to me about
the career of an artist in the 90s or
the early 2000s where it just [__] just
spread at a different pace like you
don't expect it to be this
viral thing it's just not that kind of
work no i don't i'm i'm not
again my my when i say my my goal is not
like fame and whatever it's not that i
don't like fame being like being more
popular than an average person i'm just
not shooting for some mainstream idea
like i'm not going for that if it
happens it happens but like for me i can
make a living more than i'm i'm good i'm
rich from like what i do now so like
i just want to cultivate that and make
it so that like i can make money forever
and people always support me and then if
that grows
that's perfect but like i just
understand like [__] comes in cycles and
like things happen i realistically
i just know my place i guess is what i'm
trying to say and i just i want to go
further but i'm good to where i'm at
right now so yeah i look at [__] like
that because it's better to know
reality than walk around us making an
assumption or just having a big head
about some [__] that's not real right
how often do you think about how you're
going to be remembered when you're gone
like how much of a consideration is that
all the time actually
i think about a i think a lot of the
stuff i do is meant to be consumed
long term like in retrospect you know
how we we discover weird music and it
comes back in cycle and like [__] like
that i feel like
not that i want to be one of those
people but like maybe i would be or like
i hope i would be but like i think about
it all the time because i want to be
remembered that's why i work so hard on
the music because when you're dead
um
unless you had a personality that was
just so so big
your music will be left and people will
dissect it and like i want it to be
respectable you know what i mean i want
people to look back and be like this
[__] was on people can think i'm
weird whatever right now but i want
people to look back and be like this
[__] was on his [__] he wasn't
weird he was just like technical as [__]
that's crazy that you could be happy
right now in advance of the fact that
you know that when you're gone there's
gonna be some kid listening to your
music and being inspired by it and that
that informs your whole world view right
now even though that hasn't happened yet
yet because it will because it happened
to me i was inspired by like some weird
[__] who like maybe wasn't like
huge back in the day and they
made me do what i'm doing right now so
that's why i'm just excited about it
like
you know it happens all the time dude
like there's an artist named nick drake
he died nobody nobody knew who this
[__] was he played a show to
like 70 people and then
od'd in his house nobody even found him
for like a day
20 years later they put his song in like
a truck commercial or some [__] and now
everybody
there's a bunch of artists that sound
just like nick drake wow he has his own
like influence palette but he'll never
know because he's [__] he [__]
died thinking he's a nobody you know
what i'm saying that's crazy i just
don't want to walk around thinking i'm
i'm nobody or i didn't you know i'm not
as big as this person or that person
right i just i want to
be
uh was it not complacent but i want to
be happy in the fact that like i might
have influenced somebody to do this or
that and that's cool and i can make
enough money to do what i want to do i'm
completely satisfied
well i'm completely satisfied with this
interview because this is a fascinating
guy right here and i like your attitude
my man
thank you man i appreciate it i
appreciate you doing this for me man oh
yeah appreciate it man jpeg mafia
excellent interview i really appreciate
that man
no jumper coolest podcast in the world
check us out on youtube and all that
like comment subscribe no jumper.com if
you want to support and uh go turn my
man up on services of your choice
yup i'm sure you can guess i don't know
which camera to look at but
something pisses me off about shouting
out itunes and spotify at the end of
every episode you know
they don't need that you know where the
music is it feels very inauthentic well
yeah yeah you can just say out
everywhere you don't have to be specific